This is what I mean by people not
profit. This is the first Airbnb I ever
bought in my life. But when I bought it,
I wasn't thinking about making money.
It's a three-bedroom, two and a half
bath little double yurt. It's an octagon
with exposed framing. Original artwork
from my homie Austin Atkins, rest in
peace. It's got a wrap-around porch
that's situated right here in the
Cherokee National Forest. Peekaboo views
of Pine Mountain right through the tree
line. Plus, right down there is the
Appalachian Trail and Watauga Lake.
Listen, half a mile, absolutely perfect
for outdoor lovers. I know you're saying
it's an Airbnb, what do you mean you
didn't do it for money? Well, let me
explain. I rent this secluded cabin in
the middle of the forest for $100 a
night. I made this place perfect and
rented it so cheap for one reason, so
people will come here Look at this. And
love the outdoors as much as I do. I
love you. Cuz if there's nobody that
loves Mother Earth, Arthur, there'll be
nobody to stand up and say no. My little
girl and my little boy Mikey. And the
gas man or the timber man or the oil man
comes to say, "I'm going to cut your
forest down." I think this one's my
favorite. I'm going to grill in the
lake. Family memories. Nah, man. Sign
your name. Make your mark. Save the
memory forever. You have to affect
people with your actions, and that's why
I bought this Airbnb. If you look at the
wall, it's working. This makes me
happier than anything else. Seeing my
wall of fame loaded down with happy
people. It kind of makes me want to cry
to know that I've touched this many
people's lives just through a house.